Sam B. Hall, Jr. Papers, Inclusive: 1943-2005, undated Bulk: 1976-1985
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1965-1985, undated; 8
  - Dear Colleague, 1975-1985; 4
    - Bills to be Cosponsored (2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 437, Folder 2)
    - Bills to be Cosponsored (3 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 437, Folder 3)
    - Dear Colleague, 1984-1985 (Box 437, Folder 4)
    - Dear Colleague, 1985 (Box 437, Folder 5)
  - Program Files, 1978-1985; 5
    The Program Files subseries contains daily Legislative Program agendas, Democratic Study Group (DSG) Report, the Whip Advisory, and special interest correspondence related to matters scheduled for debate. The subseries is arranged chronologically with each file representing one week from July 1978 to September 1985. The material is in good condition.
    - General, 1978 July 14-31 (Box 438, Folder 1)
    - General, 1978 August 1-9 (Box 438, Folder 2)
    - General, 1978 August 10 (Box 438, Folder 3)
    - General, 1978 August 11-17 (Box 438, Folder 4)
    - General, 1978 September 6 (Box 438, Folder 5)
    - General, 1978 September 7-11 (Box 438, Folder 6)
    - General, 1978 September 13-18 (Box 439, Folder 1)
    - General, 1978 September 19-20 (Box 439, Folder 2)
    - General, 1978 September 21-22 (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - General, 1978 September 25-26 (Box 439, Folder 4)
    - General, 1978 September 27 (Box 439, Folder 5)
    - General, 1978 October 2 (Box 439, Folder 6)
    - General, 1978 October 5-9 (Box 439, Folder 7)
    - General, 1978 October 13 (Box 440, Folder 1)
    - General, 1979 February 26- March 4 (Box 440, Folder 2)
    - General, 1979 March 5-18 (Box 440, Folder 3)
    - General, 1979 March 19-April 1 (Box 440, Folder 4)
    - General, 1979 March 26-April 1 (Box 440, Folder 5)
    - General, 1979 April 2-8 (Box 440, Folder 6)
    - General, 1979 April 23-29 (Box 440, Folder 7)
    - Committee Meeting (Ethics), 1979 April 24 (Box 440, Folder 8)
    - General, 1979 April 30-May 6 (Box 441, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 3), 1979 May 7-13 (Box 441, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 3), 1979 May 7-13 (Box 441, Folder 3)
    - General (3 of 3), 1979 May 7-13 (Box 441, Folder 4)
    - General, 1979 May 14-20 (Box 441, Folder 5)
    - General, 1979 May 21-27 (Box 441, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 2), 1979 May 28- June 3 (Box 441, Folder 7)
    - General (2 of 2), 1979 May 28- June 3 (Box 441, Folder 8)
    - General (1 of 2), 1979 June 4-10 (Box 441, Folder 9)
    - General (2 of 2), 1979 June 4-10 (Box 442, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 2), 1979 June 11-17 (Box 442, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 2), 1979 June 11-17 (Box 442, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 3), 1979 June 18-24 (Box 442, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 3), 1979 June 18-24 (Box 442, Folder 5)
    - General (3 of 3), 1979 June 18-24 (Box 442, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 3), 1979 June 25-July 1 (Box 442, Folder 7)
    - General (2 of 3), 1979 June 25-July 1 (Box 443, Folder 1)
    - General (3 of 3), 1979 June 25-July 1 (Box 443, Folder 2)
    - General, 1979 July 2-8 (Box 443, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 2), 1979 July 9-15 (Box 443, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 2), 1979 July 9-15 (Box 443, Folder 5)
    - General (1 of 3), 1979 July 16-22 (Box 443, Folder 6)
    - General (2 of 3), 1979 July 16-22 (Box 443, Folder 7)
    - General (3 of 3), 1979 July 16-22 (Box 444, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 2), 1979 July 23-29 (Box 444, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 2), 1979 July 23-29 (Box 444, Folder 3)
    - General, 1979 July 26 (Box 444, Folder 4)
    - General, 1979 July 30-August 5 (Box 444, Folder 5)
    - General, 1979 September 3-9 (Box 444, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 2), 1979 September 10-16 (Box 444, Folder 7)
    - General (2 of 2), 1979 September 10-16 (Box 445, Folder 1)
    - Judiciary Committee Material, 1979 September 10 (Box 445, Folder 2)
    - General, 1979 September 13-17 (Box 445, Folder 3)
    - General, 1979 September 14-November 28 (Box 445, Folder 4)
    - General (1 of 4), 1979 September 17-23 (Box 445, Folder 5)
    - General (2 of 4), 1979 September 17-23 (Box 445, Folder 6)
    - General (3 of 4), 1979 September 17-23 (Box 445, Folder 7)
    - General (4 of 4), 1979 September 17-23 (Box 445, Folder 8)
    - General, 1979 September 19-20 (Box 445, Folder 9)
    - General (1 of 3), 1979 September 24-30 (Box 445, Folder 10)
    - General (2 of 3), 1979 September 24-30 (Box 446, Folder 1)
    - General (3 of 3), 1979 September 24-30 (Box 446, Folder 2)
    - General, 1979 September 27 (Box 446, Folder 3)
    - General, 1979 October 8-14 (Box 446, Folder 4)
    - General, 1979 October 11-12 (Box 446, Folder 5)
    - General (1 of 5), 1979 October 15-21 (Box 446, Folder 6)
    - General (2 of 5), 1979 October 15-21 (Box 446, Folder 7)
    - General (3 of 5), 1979 October 15-21 (Box 446, Folder 8)
    - General (4 of 5), 1979 October 15-21 (Box 447, Folder 1)
    - General (5 of 5), 1979 October 15-21 (Box 447, Folder 2)
    - General, 1979 October 18 (Box 447, Folder 3)
    - General, 1979 October 22-28 (Box 447, Folder 4)
    - Veterans’ Affairs, 1979 October 25 (Box 447, Folder 5)
    - General, 1979 October 29- November 4 (Box 447, Folder 6)
    - Priority Energy Act, 1979 October 29- November 4 (Box 448, Folder 1)
    - General, 1979 November 1 (Box 448, Folder 2)
    - General, 1979 November 5-11 (Box 448, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 4), 1979 November 12-18 (Box 448, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 4), 1979 November 12-18 (Box 448, Folder 5)
    - General (3 of 4), 1979 November 12-18 (Box 448, Folder 6)
    - General (4 of 4), 1979 November 12-18 (Box 448, Folder 7)
    - General, 1979 November 16 (Box 448, Folder 8)
    - General, 1979 November 26-December 2 (Box 448, Folder 9)
    - General (1 of 2), 1979 December 3-9 (Box 448, Folder 10)
    - General (2 of 2), 1979 December 3-9 (Box 449, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 2), 1979 December 10-16 (Box 449, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 2), 1979 December 10-16 (Box 449, Folder 3)
    - General, 1979 December 17-23 (Box 449, Folder 4)
    - General, 1979 December 18-20 (Box 449, Folder 5)
    - General, 1980 January 21-23 (Box 449, Folder 6)
    - General, 1980 January 28-February 4 (Box 449, Folder 7)
    - General (1 of 2), 1980 February 4-10 (Box 449, Folder 8)
    - General (2 of 2), 1980 February 4-10 (Box 449, Folder 9)
    - General, 1980 February 4-March 4 (Box 450, Folder 1)
    - General, 1980 February 11 (Box 450, Folder 2)
    - General, 1980 February 14-18 (Box 450, Folder 3)
    - General, 1980 February 21-25 (Box 450, Folder 4)
    - General, 1980 February 28-March 3 (Box 450, Folder 5)
    - General, 1980 March 4 (Box 450, Folder 6)
    - General, 1980 March 5 (Box 450, Folder 7)
    - General, 1980 March 10-16 (Box 451, Folder 1)
    - General, 1980 March 13 (Box 451, Folder 2)
    - General, 1980 March 17 (Box 451, Folder 3)
    - General, 1980 March 18-26 (Box 451, Folder 4)
    - General, 1980 March 31 (Box 451, Folder 5)
    - General, 1980 April 1-16 (Box 451, Folder 6)
    - General, 1980 April 17 (Box 451, Folder 7)
    - General, 1980 April 21-22 (Box 451, Folder 8)
    - General, 1980 April 24-28 (Box 451, Folder 9)
    - General, 1980 May 5 (Box 452, Folder 1)
    - General, 1980 May 7-8 (Box 452, Folder 2)
    - General, 1980 May 12-18 (Box 452, Folder 3)
    - General, 1980 May 15-16 (Box 452, Folder 4)
    - General, 1980 May 19-21 (Box 452, Folder 5)
    - General, 1980 May 22 (Box 452, Folder 6)
    - General, 1980 May 26-28 (Box 452, Folder 7)
    - General, 1980 May 29-30 (Box 452, Folder 8)
    - General, 1980 June 3-5 (Box 452, Folder 9)
    - General, 1980 June 9-10 (Box 452, Folder 10)
    - General, 1980 June 12-13 (Box 452, Folder 11)
    - General, 1980 June 16 (Box 452, Folder 12)
    - General, 1980 June 19 (Box 453, Folder 1)
    - General, 1980 June 20-25 (Box 453, Folder 2)
    - General, 1980 June 30 (Box 453, Folder 3)
    - General, 1980 July 1 (Box 453, Folder 4)
    - General, 1980 July 21-24 (Box 453, Folder 5)
    - General, 1980 July 24 (Box 453, Folder 6)
    - General, 1980 July 31 (Box 453, Folder 7)
    - General, 1980 August 18 (Box 454, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 2), 1980 August 18 September 5 (Box 454, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 2), 1980 August 18 September 5 (Box 454, Folder 3)
    - General, 1980 August 19 (Box 454, Folder 4)
    - General, 1980 August 20 (Box 454, Folder 5)
    - General, 1980 August 20-September 20 (Box 454, Folder 6)
    - General, 1980 September 1-7 (Box 454, Folder 7)
    - General, 1980 September 4 (Box 454, Folder 8)
    - General, 1980 September 8-14 (Box 454, Folder 9)
    - General, 1980 September 8 (Box 454, Folder 10)
    - General, 1980 September 8-13 (Box 454, Folder 11)
    - General (1 of 4), 1980 September 9 (Box 454, Folder 12)
    - General (2 of 4), 1980 September 9 (Box 455, Folder 1)
    - General (3 of 4), 1980 September 9 (Box 455, Folder 2)
    - General (4 of 4), 1980 September 9 (Box 455, Folder 3)
    - General, 1980 September 15-21 (Box 455, Folder 4)
    - General, 1980 September 22-28 (Box 455, Folder 5)
    - General, 1980 September 25 (Box 455, Folder 6)
    - General, 1980 September 29-October 5 (Box 455, Folder 7)
    - General, 1981 January 5- February 23 (Box 455, Folder 8)
    - General, 1981 February 24 March 3 (Box 455, Folder 9)
    - General, 1981 March 23-29 (Box 456, Folder 1)
    - General, 1981 March 23-24 (Box 456, Folder 2)
    - General, 1981 March 25-26 (Box 456, Folder 3)
    - General, 1981 April 6 (Box 456, Folder 4)
    - General, 1981 April 30 (Box 456, Folder 5)
    - FY 1982 Budget Resolution, 1981 May 4-6 (Box 456, Folder 6)
    - General, 1981 May 7 (Box 456, Folder 7)
    - General, 1981 May 12-18 (Box 456, Folder 8)
    - General, 1981 May 19-28 (Box 456, Folder 9)
    - General, 1981 June 2 (Box 456, Folder 10)
    - General, 1981 June 4-11 (Box 457, Folder 1)
    - General, 1981 June 15-22 (Box 457, Folder 2)
    - General, 1981 June 23 (Box 457, Folder 3)
    - General, 1981 June 24-25 (Box 457, Folder 4)
    - General, 1981 June 26 (Box 457, Folder 5)
    - General, 1981 July 9-10 (Box 457, Folder 6)
    - General, 1981 July 13 (Box 457, Folder 7)
    - General, 1981 July 14 (Box 457, Folder 8)
    - General, 1981 July 15 (Box 457, Folder 9)
    - General, 1981 July 16 (Box 457, Folder 10)
    - General, 1981 July 17 (Box 457, Folder 11)
    - General, 1981 July 21 (Box 457, Folder 12)
    - General, 1981 July 22-23 (Box 457, Folder 13)
    - General, 1981 July 27 (Box 458, Folder 1)
    - General, 1981 July 28 (Box 458, Folder 2)
    - General (1 of 2), 1981 July 29 (Box 458, Folder 3)
    - General (2 of 2), 1981 July 29 (Box 458, Folder 4)
    - General, 1981 July 31 (Box 458, Folder 5)
    - General, 1981 July 30- August 4 (Box 458, Folder 6)
    - General, 1981 September 9-15 (Box 458, Folder 7)
    - General, 1981 September 16-21 (Box 458, Folder 8)
    - General, 1981 September 22 (Box 458, Folder 9)
    - General, 1981 September 23-24 (Box 458, Folder 10)
    - General, 1981 September 28- October 4 (Box 459, Folder 1)
    - General, 1981 September 28-30 (Box 459, Folder 2)
    - General, 1981 October 1 (Box 459, Folder 3)
    - General, 1981 October 5 (Box 459, Folder 4)
    - General, 1981 October 7-14 (Box 459, Folder 5)
    - General, 1981 October 15 (Box 459, Folder 6)
    - General, 1981 October 19-27 (Box 459, Folder 7)
    - General, 1981 October 28 (Box 459, Folder 8)
    - General, 1981 November 4 (Box 459, Folder 9)
    - General, 1981 November 5-12 (Box 459, Folder 10)
    - General, 1981 November 16 (Box 459, Folder 11)
    - General, 1981 November 17 (Box 459, Folder 12)
    - General, 1981 November 18 (Box 459, Folder 13)
    - General, 1981 November 19-20 (Box 459, Folder 14)
    - General, 1981 December 7-13 (Box 459, Folder 15)
    - General, 1981 December 8 (Box 459, Folder 16)
    - General, 1982 February 9-10 (Box 459, Folder 17)
    - General, 1982 March 2-10 (Box 460, Folder 1)
    - General, 1982 March 31 (Box 460, Folder 2)
    - General, 1982 May 4-6 (Box 460, Folder 3)
    - General, 1982 May 10-11 (Box 460, Folder 4)
    - General, 1982 May 13 (Box 460, Folder 5)
    - General, 1982 May 18-19 (Box 460, Folder 6)
    - General, 1982 May 20-23 (Box 460, Folder 7)
    - Budget Resolution, 1982 May 24 (Box 460, Folder 8)
    - General, 1982 May 25 (Box 460, Folder 9)
    - General, 1982 May 26 (Box 460, Folder 10)
    - General, 1982 May 27 (Box 460, Folder 11)
    - General, 1982 June 2-9 (Box 460, Folder 12)
    - General, 1982 June 10 (Box 460, Folder 13)
    - General, 1982 June 14 (Box 460, Folder 14)
    - General, 1982 June 15-21 (Box 460, Folder 15)
    - General, 1982 June 22 (Box 460, Folder 16)
    - General (1 of 2), 1982 June 23 (Box 461, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 2), 1982 June 23 (Box 461, Folder 2)
    - General, 1982 July 12-15 (Box 461, Folder 3)
    - General, 1982 July 19 (Box 461, Folder 4)
    - General, 1982 July 22 (Box 461, Folder 5)
    - General, 1982 July 24 (Box 461, Folder 6)
    - General, 1982 July 27 (Box 461, Folder 7)
    - General, 1982 July 29 (Box 461, Folder 8)
    - General, 1982 August 2-5 (Box 461, Folder 9)
    - General, 1982 August 9-10 (Box 461, Folder 10)
    - General (1 of 2), 1982 August 11 (Box 461, Folder 11)
    - General (2 of 2), 1982 August 11 (Box 461, Folder 12)
    - General, 1982 August 12 (Box 461, Folder 13)
    - General, 1982 August 13-16 (Box 461, Folder 14)
    - General, 1982 August 17 (Box 461, Folder 15)
    - General, 1982 August 18 (Box 462, Folder 1)
    - General, 1982 August 19 (Box 462, Folder 2)
    - General, 1982 September 8 (Box 462, Folder 3)
    - General, 1982 September 9 (Box 462, Folder 4)
    - General, 1982 September 14 (Box 462, Folder 5)
    - General, 1982 September 15 (Box 462, Folder 6)
    - General, 1982 September 16 (Box 462, Folder 7)
    - General, 1982 September 20 (Box 462, Folder 8)
    - General, 1982 September 21 (Box 462, Folder 9)
    - General, 1982 September 22-24 (Box 462, Folder 10)
    - General, 1982 September 28 (Box 462, Folder 11)
    - General, 1982 September 29 (Box 462, Folder 12)
    - General, 1982 October 1 (Box 462, Folder 13)
    - General, 1982 November 29-December 1 (Box 463, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 2), 1982 December 2 (Box 463, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 2), 1982 December 2 (Box 463, Folder 3)
    - General, 1982 December 8 (Box 463, Folder 4)
    - General, 1982 December 9 (Box 463, Folder 5)
    - General, 1982 December 13-14 (Box 463, Folder 6)
    - General, 1982 December 15-16 (Box 463, Folder 7)
    - General, 1982 December 17 (Box 463, Folder 8)
    - General, 1982 December 18-20 (Box 463, Folder 9)
    - General, 1983 January 3 (Box 463, Folder 10)
    - General, 1983 March 3 (Box 463, Folder 11)
    - General, 1983 March 3-8 (Box 463, Folder 12)
    - General, 1983 March 9 (Box 464, Folder 1)
    - General, 1983 March 9-16 (Box 464, Folder 2)
    - General, 1983 March 21-22 (Box 464, Folder 3)
    - General, 1983 March 23 (Box 464, Folder 4)
    - General, 1983 March 24 (Box 464, Folder 5)
    - General, 1983 April 12 (Box 464, Folder 6)
    - General, 1983 April 20-28 (Box 464, Folder 7)
    - General, 1983 May 3 (Box 464, Folder 8)
    - General, 1983 May 4 (Box 464, Folder 9)
    - General, 1983 May 9 (Box 464, Folder 10)
    - General, 1983 May 10 (Box 464, Folder 11)
    - General, 1983 May 12 (Box 464, Folder 12)
    - General, 1983 May 17 (Box 464, Folder 13)
    - General, 1983 May 18-26 (Box 465, Folder 1)
    - General, 1983 June 1-2 (Box 465, Folder 2)
    - General, 1983 June 3-6 (Box 465, Folder 3)
    - General, 1983 June 7 (Box 465, Folder 4)
    - General, 1983 June 8 (Box 465, Folder 5)
    - General, 1983 June 9 (Box 465, Folder 6)
    - General, 1983 June 13-14 (Box 465, Folder 7)
    - General, 1983 June 15 (Box 465, Folder 8)
    - General, 1983 June 21-23 (Box 465, Folder 9)
    - General, 1983 June 23 (Box 465, Folder 10)
    - General, 1983 June 27-28 (Box 465, Folder 11)
    - General, 1983 June 29 (Box 465, Folder 12)
    - General, 1983 June 30 (Box 465, Folder 13)
    - General, 1983 July 11 (Box 465, Folder 14)
    - General, 1983 July 12 (Box 465, Folder 15)
    - General, 1983 July 13 (Box 465, Folder 16)
    - General, 1983 July 14 (Box 465, Folder 17)
    - General, 1983 July 18-19 (Box 465, Folder 18)
    - General, 1983 July 20 (Box 466, Folder 1)
    - General, 1983 July 21 (Box 466, Folder 2)
    - General, 1983 July 25 (Box 466, Folder 3)
    - General, 1983 July 26 (Box 466, Folder 4)
    - General, 1983 July 27-28 (Box 466, Folder 5)
    - General, 1983 July 29 (Box 466, Folder 6)
    - General, 1983 August 1 (Box 466, Folder 7)
    - General, 1983 August 2 (Box 466, Folder 8)
    - General, 1983 August 3 (Box 466, Folder 9)
    - General, 1983 August 4 (Box 466, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Digest, House Republican Conference, 1983 September - November (Box 466, Folder 11)
    - General, 1983 September 12 (Box 466, Folder 12)
    - General, 1983 September 14-15 (Box 466, Folder 13)
    - General, 1983 September 19-20 (Box 466, Folder 14)
    - General, 1983 September 21-22 (Box 467, Folder 1)
    - General, 1983 September 26 (Box 467, Folder 2)
    - General, 1983 September 27 (Box 467, Folder 3)
    - General, 1983 September 28 (Box 467, Folder 4)
    - General, 1983 September 29-30 (Box 467, Folder 5)
    - General, 1983 October 3 (Box 467, Folder 6)
    - General, 1983 October 4-31 (Box 467, Folder 7)
    - General, 1983 October 4-5 (Box 467, Folder 8)
    - General, 1983 October 6 (Box 467, Folder 9)
    - General, 1983 October 18-21 (Box 467, Folder 10)
    - General, 1983 October 24-25 (Box 467, Folder 11)
    - General, 1983 October 26 (Box 467, Folder 12)
    - General, 1983 October 27 (Box 467, Folder 13)
    - General, 1983 October 31 (Box 467, Folder 14)
    - General, 1983 November 3 (Box 467, Folder 15)
    - General, 1983 November 4 (Box 468, Folder 1)
    - General, 1983 November 7 (Box 468, Folder 2)
    - General, 1983 November 8 (Box 468, Folder 3)
    - General, 1983 November 9 (Box 468, Folder 4)
    - General, 1983 November 10 (Box 468, Folder 5)
    - General, 1983 November 14 (Box 468, Folder 6)
    - General, 1983 November 15 (Box 468, Folder 7)
    - General, 1983 November 16 (Box 468, Folder 8)
    - General, 1983 November 17 (Box 468, Folder 9)
    - General, 1983 November 18 (Box 468, Folder 10)
    - General, 1984 January 24-25 (Box 468, Folder 11)
    - General, 1984 January 26 (Box 468, Folder 12)
    - General, 1984 January 30-31 (Box 468, Folder 13)
    - General, 1984 February 1-6 (Box 468, Folder 14)
    - General, 1984 February 7-9 (Box 468, Folder 15)
    - General, 1984 February 21-29 (Box 468, Folder 16)
    - General, 1984 March 1 (Box 468, Folder 17)
    - General, 1984 March 5-8 (Box 469, Folder 1)
    - General, 1984 March 13-15 (Box 469, Folder 2)
    - General, 1984 March 20 (Box 469, Folder 3)
    - General, 1984 March 21 (Box 469, Folder 4)
    - General, 1984 March 22-27 (Box 469, Folder 5)
    - General, 1984 March 28-29 (Box 469, Folder 6)
    - General, 1984 April 2-3 (Box 469, Folder 7)
    - General, 1984 April 5 (Box 469, Folder 8)
    - General, 1984 April 9-11 (Box 469, Folder 9)
    - General, 1984 April 12 (Box 469, Folder 10)
    - General, 1984 April 24-26 (Box 469, Folder 11)
    - General, 1984 May 1 (Box 469, Folder 12)
    - General, 1984 May 2-3 (Box 469, Folder 13)
    - General, 1984 May 7 (Box 469, Folder 14)
    - General, 1984 May 8 (Box 469, Folder 15)
    - General (1 of 2), 1984 May 9 (Box 469, Folder 16)
    - General (2 of 2), 1984 May 9 (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - General, 1984 May 10 (Box 470, Folder 2)
    - General, 1984 May 15 (Box 470, Folder 3)
    - General, 1984 May 17 (Box 470, Folder 4)
    - General, 1984 May 21 (Box 470, Folder 5)
    - General, 1984 May 22 (Box 470, Folder 6)
    - General, 1984 May 23-24 (Box 470, Folder 7)
    - General, 1984 May 30 (Box 470, Folder 8)
    - General, 1984 May 31 (Box 470, Folder 9)
    - General, 1984 June 7-18 (Box 470, Folder 10)
    - General, 1984 June 19 (Box 470, Folder 11)
    - General (1 of 2), 1984 June 20 (Box 470, Folder 12)
    - General (2 of 2), 1984 June 20 (Box 470, Folder 13)
    - General, 1984 June 21 (Box 470, Folder 14)
    - General, 1984 June 22 (Box 470, Folder 15)
    - General, 1984 June 26 (Box 470, Folder 16)
    - General, 1984 June 27 (Box 471, Folder 1)
    - General, 1984 June 28 (Box 471, Folder 2)
    - General, 1984 June 29 (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - General, 1984 July 24 (Box 471, Folder 4)
    - General, 1984 July 25 (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - General (1 of 2), 1984 July 26 (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - General (2 of 2), 1984 July 26 (Box 471, Folder 7)
    - General, 1984 July 30-31 (Box 471, Folder 8)
    - Hunger Relief Act, 1984 July 31 (Box 471, Folder 9)
    - General, 1984 July 31 (Box 471, Folder 10)
    - General, 1984 August 1 (Box 471, Folder 11)
    - General (1 of 2), 1984 August 2 (Box 471, Folder 12)
    - General (2 of 2), 1984 August 2 (Box 471, Folder 13)
    - General, 1984 August 6 (Box 471, Folder 14)
    - General, 1984 August 8 (Box 471, Folder 15)
    - General, 1984 September 5 (Box 472, Folder 1)
    - General, 1984 September 12-13 (Box 472, Folder 2)
    - General, 1984 September 14 (Box 472, Folder 3)
    - General, 1984 September 17 (Box 472, Folder 4)
    - General, 1984 September 18 (Box 472, Folder 5)
    - General, 1984 September 19 (Box 472, Folder 6)
    - General, 1984 September 20 (Box 472, Folder 7)
    - General, 1984 September 25 (Box 472, Folder 8)
    - General, 1984 October 1 (Box 472, Folder 9)
    - General, 1984 October 2 (Box 472, Folder 10)
    - General, 1984 October 3-8 (Box 472, Folder 11)
    - General, 1984 October 10 (Box 472, Folder 12)
    - General, 1985 January 3 (Box 472, Folder 13)
    - General, 1985 January 30 (Box 472, Folder 14)
    - General (1 of 2), 1985 February 7 (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 2), 1985 February 7 (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - General, 1985 February 21-27 (Box 473, Folder 3)
    - General, 1985 February 26 (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - General, 1985 March 4-5 (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - General, 1985 March 7 (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - General, 1985 March 19 (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - General, 1985 March 26 (Box 473, Folder 8)
    - General, 1985 March 28 (Box 473, Folder 9)
    - General, 1985 April 2-3 (Box 473, Folder 10)
    - General, 1985 April 16-18 (Box 473, Folder 11)
    - General, 1985 April 23 (Box 473, Folder 12)
    - General, 1985 April 30 (Box 473, Folder 13)
    - General, 1985 May 1-2 (Box 473, Folder 14)
    - General, 1985 May 6-7 (Box 473, Folder 15)
    - General, 1985 May 29 (Box 473, Folder 16)
    - General, 1985 September 6 (Box 473, Folder 17)
  - Projects, 1965-1984; 6
    The Projects subseries dates 1965-1974, and includes files inherited from Hall’s predecessor, Wright Patman. Major projects include Cooper, Big Pine, and Cypress Reservoirs. News articles, correspondence, publications, and photographs can be found on these projects as well as the Red River Bridge, Northeast Texas Resource Conservation and Development Project, and the Texarkana Urban Transportation Study. This subseries is in good condition.
    - Cypress Valley, Wright Patman File, 1965-1975 (Box 473, Folder 18)
    - Red River Bridge History (1 of 3), 1966-1976 (Box 474, Folder 1)
    - Red River Bridge History (2 of 3), 1966-1976 (Box 474, Folder 2)
    - Red River Bridge History (3 of 3), 1966-1976 (Box 474, Folder 3)
    - Northeast Texas Resource Conservation and Development Project, 1969-1979 (Box 474, Folder 4)
    - National Texas Resource Conservation and Development Project, 1969-1979 (Box 474, Folder 5)
    - Big Pine Reservoir, Patman File, 1972-1974 (Box 474, Folder 6)
    - Texarkana Urban Transportation Study, Origin Destination Survey, 1965 (Box 475, Folder 1)